evolliance.com 2013-11-30

# EVOLLIANCE |

Your privacy on the Internet is of important to us. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it. 

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Evolliance collects information about users for the purpose of providing service to users. Under no circumstances does Evolliance divulge any information to a third party. Data we request at the time of registration include: username, password, email, display name, time zone, Evony lord name, Evony alliance tag, and Evony city coordinates. 

  * **Username & passwords**: A username and password is required so that users can gain access to individual, private portals. Passwords are stored in encrypted format and are encrypted before being passed between pages. No portal admins or Evolliance staff will ever see your password in plaintext. Usernames are viewable by portal admins and Evolliance staff for the purpose of assisting users with login issues.
  * **Email** : Your email address is required for the purpose of username retrieval and password resets. This information is only visible to a limited number of Evolliance staff for the sake of assisting users.
  * **Time Zone** : Time zone is used to display information within the portal in your local time zone. It is for the convenience of the user and is optional for users to set this to their correct time zone.
  * **Evony Information** : This information is collected solely for the purpose of providing our users with a better experience while using our service.

## POLICY

**Children**  
Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. Users are required to attest that they are either 13 yrs of age or, if under the age of 13, have permission from a parent or legal guardian. 

**Usage tracking**  
Evolliance tracks user traffic patterns throughout our site. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users bur rather view usage statistics of our entire audience to improve our services and usability. 

**Cookies**  
We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided and controls our ability to provide member exclusive access to the site. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot gather data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Evolliance uses cookie files to track logged in sessions and to keep track of your choices, such as server number and alliance portal. Our advertisers may deliver a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates. 

## USE OF INFORMATION

Evolliance uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience on our site, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users. 

We do not track what individual user's access or read on the site but rather collect data on each page's performance overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (NOT including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/). We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public. 

## SHARING OF THE INFORMATION

Evolliance uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's interest. This is essential to keeping our service free. We will never sell or share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public. 

## SECURITY

Evolliance operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. 

## ACCOUNT TERMINATION

We provide users with the option to terminate any account on any portal at any time. Removing your account will remove all personal information you have provided in your profile and remove all content you have entered from being associated with your user account. 

## YOUR CONSENT

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Evolliance. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post updates on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
